<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.7.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2018-02-08T20:05:47+05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/</id><title type="html">KashifALi Notary Election Candidate</title><subtitle>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Portfolio</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2018/02/08/welcome-to-jekyll.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Portfolio" /><published>2018-02-08T17:21:58+05:00</published><updated>2018-02-08T17:21:58+05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2018/02/08/welcome-to-jekyll</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2018/02/08/welcome-to-jekyll.html">&lt;h1&gt; Introduction&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hello and Welcome to my Portfolio.&lt;p&gt; 
&lt;div&gt;My name is Kashif Ali and I'm a dedicated Software Engineer in Test/Test Automation. years of experience in software test 
development and Automation. My programming expertise include C, python, Java, Javascript, vbscript, html, APIs(soap/rest), shell programming and shell scripting &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;I had joined SuperNET technologies in 2016 as Test Engineer and have been testing IGUANA core through out, which also includes Agama wallet testing as well which was an excellent experience for me to play around stunning technologies.
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;As a Notary operator, I was elected last year as a notary operator and it was splendid experience for me but a little disappointed because 
i couldn't perform well. I'm looking forward to be a Notary operator again!&lt;/div&gt;




&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Introduction Hello and Welcome to my Portfolio. My name is Kashif Ali and I'm a dedicated Software Engineer in Test/Test Automation. years of experience in software test development and Automation. My programming expertise include C, python, Java, Javascript, vbscript, html, APIs(soap/rest), shell programming and shell scripting I had joined SuperNET technologies in 2016 as Test Engineer and have been testing IGUANA core through out, which also includes Agama wallet testing as well which was an excellent experience for me to play around stunning technologies. As a Notary operator, I was elected last year as a notary operator and it was splendid experience for me but a little disappointed because i couldn't perform well. I'm looking forward to be a Notary operator again!</summary></entry></feed>